ABOUT ME

I am a certified UI/UX Designer who believes in design as a process of problem solving by learning about it, exploring new ideas, putting them to test not only until it works but until its great for solving a specific need. Also, I am passionate about creating interactive and delightful experiences for the users.

CONTACT

- **** 9373171233 / 7588316776
- sharwari.design@gmail.com
- 14-B, Paras park soc, Ganesh nagar, Kathe galli, Dwarka, Nasik- 422011

PORTFOLIO - SharwariPortfolio/

CONNECT ON

Behance

https://www.behance.net/sharwarijangale

Linked in

www.linkedin.com/in/sharwari-jangale

Medium

https://medium.com/@Sharvariii07

Instagram

instagram.com/graphic.cornerr

Dribble

https://dribbble.com/Sharvariii_07

SOFTWARES

Adobe XD Figma Adobe Ilustrator Adobe dimension Adobe Photoshop Adobe After effects Adobe Lightroom Adobe Premiere Pro Wondershare Filmora

INTERESTS

Gaming Photography Cinematography Painting Mindfulness Meditation

SHARWARI JANGALE

UI/UX DESIGNER

EDUCATION

2021 - Present **UI/UX Designing**

EDIT Institute of UI/UX Designing, Pune

Diploma in UI/UX Design

2018 - 2021

Bachelors in Information

Technology

PES's Modern College of Engineering, Pune.

Savitribai Phule Pune University

CGPA: 8.07

2015 - 2018

Diploma in Computer Technology

K.K Wagh college of Polytechnic, Nasik Maharashtra State Board of Technical Education

Percentage: 81.12

EXPERIENCE

DOODLEPIE TECHNOLOGIES About - @doodlepie Technologies

(Self Employed)

UI/UX DESIGNING July 2020 - present The Deck Spaces-

A Website based on co-working spaces.

https://thedeckspaces.com/

The Pastry Saga-

A Website for a city based bakery shop.

http://www.thepastrysaga.com/

Let's play- An Application based on multiple

turf booking. (Launching soon)

Click here to see a video of working application.

Instagram - Let's Play

GRAPHIC DESIGNING

Jan 2020 - present

Logo & illustrations for websites- Amigos solvents, the real DJ's, Deep relocation

Social media posts for - @malpani_group_ @doodlepie.technologies @Let's play

Branding & packaging - @graphic.cornerr

Promotional video editing - Promo1 Promo2

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

SKILLS

Presentation

Certified Yoga Instructor

Creativity

Honesty

PERSONAL SKILLS

UI/UX, Web Designing Graphic designing

Design Thinking & Research

Project management User Empathy

Time management Information Architechture

Team work Wireframing (low, mid, high fidelity)

Communication **UI Prototyping**

Creative Problem solving

Team Building & Collaborative work

UX Mental models

Promotional Videography